// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers

let questions = [
   {
     numb: 1,
     question: "What is Magneto's real name?",
     answer: "Max Eisenhardt",
     options: [
         "Matian Eisenhardt",
         "Max Eisenhardt",
         "Jakob Eisenhardt",
         "Magnus Eisenhardt"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 2,
     question: "The group of teenagers with special ability is known as?",
     answer: "The New Mutants",
     options: [
         "The Gifted Mutants",
         "The Class of Mutants",
         "The New Mutants",
         "The Old Mutants"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 3,
     question: "What name is Wolverine also known by?",
     answer: "Logan",
     options: [
         "Logan",
         "Gogan",
         "Dogan",
         "Hogan"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 4,
     question: "What does the special eyewear do for Cyclops?",
     answer: "Control the energy beams",
     options: [
         "Transform the energy beams",
         "Enhances the energy beams",
         "Disable the energy beams",
         "Control the energy beams"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 5,
     question: "What is the name of the school that Professor X bet up for young Mutants?",
     answer: "The Xavier's School for Gifted Youngsters",
     options: [
         "The Xavier's School for Mutants",
         "The Xavier's School for Gifted Youngsters",
         "Xavier Mutant protection program",
         "Xavier gifted youngster protection school"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which X-Men did Ian McKellen play?",
     answer: "Magneto",
     options: [
         "Quicksilver",
         "Professor Xavier",
         "Night crowler",
         "Magneto"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "What is the name of X-Men character that can freeze anything?",
     answer: "Ice-Man",
     options: [
         "Frost",
         "Ice-Man",
         "Professor Freeze",
         "Caliban"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Who is the strongest X-Men Character?",
     answer: "Jean Grey",
     options: [
         "Jean Grey",
         "Apocalypse",
         "Jin man",
         "Steely"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Which X-Men did Halle Berry play?",
     answer: "Storm",
     options: [
         "Riptide",
         "Psylocke",
         "Jean Gey",
         "Storm"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "What did Magneto try and get Jason to do when he entered?",
     answer: "Kill all the Humans",
     options: [
         "Kill all the X-mens",
         "Kill the president of United States",
         "Kill all the Humans",
         "Destroy Cerebro"
     ]

   }



];
